Guide to the Robert Garcia papers, 1988-1993
Garcia, Robert papers, 1988-1993
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Robert Garcia papers, 1988-1993
7574
Robert Garcia
9.0 cubic feet
Personal papers, correspondence, subject files, ephemera, posters, broadsides, photographs, videos, etc.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The Robert Garcia papers include personal papers and files reflecting Garcia's personal life and involvement in lesbian and gay rights, reproductive rights, and AIDS activism. Garcia's papers also reflect his involvement in ACT UP-New York, the national organization Men of All Colors Together (formerly Black and White Men Together), and a video collective called House of Color; also, testimony regarding his arrest for civil disobedience at an ACT UP demonstration. A collection of videocassettes includes biographical material as well as footage related to activism about AIDS, identity politics, race and sexuality; also work by House of Color.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Robert Garcia was born in 1962 in Whittier, California. His years in New York City were devoted chiefly to political activism, pertaining especially to issues of race and sexuality. In "Speak for Yourself: 7 Activists Talk about ACT-UP," by Jim Hubbard, 1990, Garcia said that being half Navajo, half Mexican, and gay were the three things that identified who he was. He was an important member of ACT UP in New York City, founding and directing committees and caucuses within the organization. A leading role in ACT UP actions and demonstrations led to Garcia's participation in several video projects with the video collective House of Color. His activities extended to Latino and pro-choice activism, and included active participation in the national organization Men Of All Colors Together. He died of complications due to AIDS in New York City in 1993.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Series I. Personal
Robert Garcia's personal papers include resumes, an obituary, his memorial announcement, birth and baptismal certificates, address books, a passport, a biographical essay by his friend Karen Ramspacher, photographs, and other items pertaining to his private life. Garcia's journals date from 1985, 1988, and 1991 and include an undated journal. Garcia wrote in them sporadically, noting items of interest, and kept many loose papers within their pages. In his later journals he speaks of his impending death. Additional topics include ACT UP, his daily plans and activities, employment and finances, as well as clippings detailing Garcia's numerous appearances in the media.
Garcia's 1988 arrest on Wall Street and his subsequent testimony are included, as well as his resignation as Insurance Services Office executive secretary in 1990. Included are files Karen Rampspacher kept on Robert's health, treatments, health insurance, and the AIDS drug assistance program and files Bob Scapa, his hoyfriend during 1990-1992, kept on AIDS symptoms and other issues. Garcia kept many telephone numbers and miscellaneous notes from friends. He also had in his possession photographs of Elizabeth Taylor and James Dean, in addition to those of his family and friends. Garcia's papers included the high school diploma and photo album of fellow AIDS activist Rodger Pettyjohn.
Series II. Correspondence
Garcia's incoming correspondence is from friends and family. The familial correspondence spans approximately 1986 to 1991. The correspondence with friends begins in 1983 when Garcia was twenty-one and somewhat involved with Anthony Milanez, a man who that year wrote him numerous passionate letters. Milanez' letters abruptly stopped though Garcia received an occasional card from him from in the years 1986 to 1991. Garcia's correspondence from friends continued until 1991, and included an ex-lover Joseph Lonzi, past and present members of his New York City loft, and many other friends and acquaintances. He received a Christmas card from Phil Zwickler and post cards from Tim Miller, one of the "NEA Four" (National Endowment for the Arts artists whose grants were terminated following political pressure). Many cards and letters lack dates. In addition, a portion of his 1990 correspondence was never opened.
Series III. ACT UP
This series includes minutes, fliers, press releases, and assorted miscellany from committees Garcia was involved with such as Outreach, Majority Action, Latino Caucus, Speakers Bureau, and the Lesbian and Gay Activist History Project, as well as ACT UP publications and clippings concerning ACT UP in the media (New York) and other national and international chapters. It also includes press releases from major ACT UP protests such as the FDA Action (October 1988), Target City Hall (March 28, 1989), Storm the N.I.H. (May 21, 1990), and Stop the Church (December 10, 1989). Notable in the series are several histories of queer activism compiled by the Lesbian and Gay Activist History Project.
Series IV. AIDS
This series includes articles about the AIDS epidemic in the media, as well as such topics as drug treatment, safe sex practices, health insurance, anti-HIV discrimination, nutrition, and housing for HIV+ people. The series includes reports from the Presidential Commission on the HIV Epidemic (1987, 1988), the International Conference on AIDS (1990, 1991, 1992), and a conference regarding minorities and AIDS. The focus of Garcia's AIDS files was a critique of the United States government's handling of the AIDS crisis.
Series V. Topical Files
This series includes files Garcia kept on many other topics of interest to him, including gays and lesbians of color, women and AIDS, AIDS and New York City politics, gay Catholics, reproductive rights, gay and lesbian activism, and gay and lesbian events in the arts. Gay and lesbian activism featured in the media is prominently noted, as well as fliers and publications regarding gay and lesbian events in New York City and those held at the City's Lesbian and Gay Community Center. He kept files on a number of organizations, including his video collective, House of Color. There are files on Queer Nation, the Lesbian and Gay People of Color Steering Committee, Dignity: Gay and Lesbian Catholics, NAMBLA (North American Man/Boy Love Association)), COOL (Committee of Outraged Lesbians), WHAM (Women's Health Action and Mobilization), and MACT (Men of All Colors Together). Also included is information regarding Lesbian and Gay Studies programs implemented in colleges and universities in the United states, and conferences and events sponsored by these programs. In addition Garcia kept leaflets from Phil Zwickler and Raymond Navarro's memorial ceremonies. The series includes single issues of periodicals useful to Garcia in his research.
Series VI. Ephemera
Included in this series are gay buttons and stickers, post cards, safe sex packets, political pamphlets, matchbooks, phonodiscs, name tags, and drawings on paper napkins.
Series VII. Graphic Material
Graphic material includes posters, oversized pictorial works, and other items topically consistent with the rest of the Collection.
Series VIII. Video Material
This series includes biographical material such as the memorial tape made by Garcia's friends and a home video of this family. The videos also show Garcia and other activists talking to various audiences about AIDS, identity politics, race and sexuality. Included is work by the video collective House of Color.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Garcia, Robert.; Ramspacher, Karen.; Malus, Joan.; ACT UP-New York.; Men of All Colors Together.; National Association of Black and White Men Together.; Clit Club (New York City).
Subjects:
Civil disobedience.; AIDS (Disease)--Political activity.; AIDS (Disease)--Social unrest.; Gays--Political activity.; Reproductive rights.; Hispanic Americans.; Gay liberation movement--NewYork(City).; Race identity.; Indians of North America
Form and Genre Terms:
Videocassettes.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Robert Garcia Personal Papers
Boxes 1, 10
Series II. Correspondence
Boxes 1-2
Series III. ACT UP
Boxes 2-4, 10
Series IV. AIDS
Boxes 4-6, 10
Series V. Topical File/Research File
Boxes 6-7, 10, 11, 12
Series VI. Ephemera
Box 8
Series VII. Graphic Material
Box 9, Map Case
Series VIII. Video Material
V-110 to V-130
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Robert Garcia Personal Papers, See also under Videotapes: "Robert Garcia Memorial" (V-110), and "Our Family: The Garcias" (V-111)
  - Journals, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Journal, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
  - Journals, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
  - Journal, 1991? (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Journal, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Garcia in The Media (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Birth certificate, Baptism certificate (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Medical tests, receipts, insurance (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
  - Employment, passport, driver's license (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Employment, business cards, finances (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Memos, receipts, ACT UP plans, Lotto tickets (Box 1, Folder 13-14)
  - ACT UP notes (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - ACT UP notes (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Memos, notes, telephone numbers (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous letters and notes (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Arrest at a demonstration on Wall Street, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Testimony (Box 1, Folder 19-22)
  - Testimony, Robert Garcia's., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 20B)
  - Resignation as Insurance Services Office, Inc. (ISO) Executive Secretary, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Biographical essay by Karen Ramspacher; Miscellaneous ephemera (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Gifts (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Address book (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - James Dean address book (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Garcia in The Media (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Photographs (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Rodger Pettyjohn's high school diploma (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Rodger Pettyjohn's photo album (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Rodger Pettyjohn (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Robert Garcia Photographs (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - RG Memorial announcement, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - RG personal statement about ACT UP and RG letterhead (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Ramspacher notes on possible archives for RG's papers, 1991-1993 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Bob, Scarpa, notes on AIDS symptoms and miscellaneouns, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - ALS, Bob Scarpa to "johny Cakes," written from Cherry Grove, Fire Island, Long Island, New York, June 1991 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Bob Scarpa photographs (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Karen Ramspacher's notes about RG's health, treatment and insurance including AIDS Drug Assistrance Program, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Series II. Correspondence
  - Letters from Anthony Milanez, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Incoming letters, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Incoming letters, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Letters from family, 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Incoming letters, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Incoming letters, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Incoming letters, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Incoming letters, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Letters from family, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Incoming letters (never opened), 1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Incoming letters, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Letters from family, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Incoming letters, undated (Box 2, Folder 10-12)
  - Card from Phil Zwickler (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Series III. ACT UP
  - History (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - ACT UP: A His and Herstory of Queer Activism, June 1989 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Teach-in: Lesbian and Gay History including Daughters of Bilitis, Mattachine Society, GAA (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Personal Objectives (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - First Annual Slumber Party invitation (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Universal Healthcare (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Quilt Outreach Sign Up for FDA Action (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - New York Auction for Action (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Los Angeles (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Los Angeles (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Various national ACT UP publications (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - FDA Action, Quilt Outreach (Bus 1) Saturday, October 8, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - FDA Action, Quilt Outreach (Bus 1) Friday, October 7, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - FDA Action, Quilt Outreach (Bus 2) Saturday, October 8, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - FDA Action, Quilt Outreach (Bus 2) Saturday, Friday, October 7, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - FDA Action, Quilt Outreach (Bus 3), Saturday, October 8, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - FDA Action, Fall 1988 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Target City Hall (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - ACT UP at the N.I.H. (National Institutes of Health) (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Cardinal O'Connor and the Church (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Phone Lists (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Legislative Monitoring (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Latino Caucus (Box 2, Folder 35-36)
  - Majority Action Committee (Box 2, Folder 37-38)
  - Weekly Reports (Box 2, Folder 39-40)
  - Outreach Committee (Box 2, Folder 41-44)
  - Outreach Duties (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Speakers Bureau (Box 2, Folder 46-49)
  - Speakers Bureau (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Speaking Engagements (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Media Committee (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Media Committee (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
  - Housing Caucus, Homeless People with AIDS (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - ZAP Fact Sheets (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Project Database (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Benefits for ACT UP (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material (Box 3, Folder 8-41)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
  - ACT UP Enquirer (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - San Francisco (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Los Angeles (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Los Angeles (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Los Angeles News (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Reports (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
  - AIDS Drugs Now (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - ACT UP's Checklist for Actions (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Mailing List (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - New York Women's Caucus (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Treatment and Data Update (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Treatment and Data Update (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Treatment and Data (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - ACT UP at the Oscars (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - International ACT UP (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - ACT UP, General (Box 10, Folder 6-11)
- Series IV. AIDS
  - Clinical Trial Groups (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Insurance and AIDS (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Directories: Lesbian/Gay, AIDS (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Politics (Box 4, Folder 20-26)
  - Politics (Box 10, Folder 12-16)
  - Presidential Commission on HIV Epidemic (Box 4, Folder 27-30)
  - Presidential Commission on HIV Epidemic, Washington, D.C., March 3, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Presidential commission on HIV Epidemic, Washington, D.C., January 11, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Presidential commission on HIV Epidemic, Washington, D.C., February 29, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Los Angeles Policy on HIV/AIDS Epidemic (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - The Macro-Metabolic Eating System (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - New York State Directory of AIDS/HIV Clinical Trials, Fall 1991 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - AIDS Related Services/Education Proposal, New York City, 1988-89 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Advance Program: 6th International Conference on AIDS, San Francisco, California, June 20-24, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - VII International Conference on AIDS, Florence, Italy, June 16-21, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - VIII International Conference on AIDS, Amsterdam, The Netherlands, July 19-24, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - FDA Action Handbook (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Critique of AIDS Clinical Trials Group, May 1, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - GMHC: AIDS Service and Education Foundation Annual Report, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Second International Lesbian and Gay Health Conference and AIDS Forum Boston, Mass., July 20-26, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Government AIDS Treatment Programs (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - ACT UP: Glossary of AIDS Drug Trials Testing of Treatment Issues (Box 4, Folder 46-47)
  - Heroin and Cocaine Trafficking and the Relationship between IV Drug Use and AIDS, Nov. 26, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Intravenous Substance Abuse and AIDS Prevention Act of 1987 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Pediatric AIDS Hearing, July 27, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - AIDS Education, Information, Risk Reduction, Training, Prevention, Treatment, Care and Research Act of 1987 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - "AIDS Drugs: Where are they?" 73rd Report by the Committee on Government Operations (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - HEAL (Health Education AIDS Liaison) (Box 4, Folder 53-54)
  - HEAL (Health Education AIDS Liaison) (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Minority Acquired Immunodeficiency Syndrome Awareness and Prevention Act of 1987 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Intravenous Substance Abuse and AIDS Prevention Act of 1987 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - National Conference on Prevention of HIV Infection and AIDS Among Racial and Ethnic Minorities in United States, August 15-17, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - New York AIDS Coalition Conference, Albany, New York, October 18-19, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Letters from House of Representatives requesting sponsorship of various AIDS-related bills (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Drug Trials and Treatment Information, Nutritional Programs (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Treatment Decisions Handbook (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - FDA Action Handbook, Sept. 21, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Funding Agenda for Community Based HIV/AIDS Programs in New York City (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Funding Agenda for Community Based HIV/AIDS Programs in New York State, Nov. 1988 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Funding Agenda for Community Based HIV/AIDS Programs in New York State, Dec. 1988 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - The Economic and Policy Implications of Early Intervention in HIV Disease (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Centers for Disease Control (CDC) HIV/AIDS Surveillance, July 1989 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - AIDS and the Black Community (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Gay/Lesbians of Color and AIDS (Box 5, Folder 14-15)
  - Lesbians and AIDS (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Women and AIDS (Box 5, Folder 17-18)
  - NAMES Project Quilt (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - AIDS and Syphilis (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - AIDS and Reproductive Rights (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - U.S. Commission of Civil Rights and AIDS (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - New York City AIDS Task Force (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - AIDS Public Information Data Set (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - AIDS and New York City (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - National Conference on HIV Infection and AIDS Among Racial and Ethnic Populations (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Summary of Findings: National HIV Research Study of Black Men (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material (Box 5, Folder 27-48)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Material (Box 6, Folder 1-28)
  - AIDS (Box 10, Folder 12-16)
- Series V. Topical File/Research File
  - PFLAG (Parents and Friends of Lesbians and Gays) (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Lesbian and Gay Activism: Bibliography (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Gay/Lesbian Activism (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Lesbian and Gay Studies (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Stonewall Community Foundation (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - National Association of Social Workers Resource Directory re: Lesbians and Gays (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Events in the Arts (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Gay/Lesbian Events in the Arts (Box 10, Folder 21-22)
  - "Group Material," an artist's collective (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Keith Haring (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Censorship in the Arts (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Compound Q (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - VOCAL (Voices of Color Against AIDS and for Life) (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - The Community Research Initiative (CRI) (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Queer Nation (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Queer Nation (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - TIARRA (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - House of Color (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - House of Color II (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Mission Statement: Lesbian and Gay People of Color Steering Committee (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Lesbian and Gay People of Color Steering Committee (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - International News Concerning Gay/Lesbian Issues (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - New York City Council Politics (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - New York City Council Politics (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Gay Catholics (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Dignity: Gay and Lesbian Catholics (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Gay/Lesbian Events in the Arts (Box 7, Folder 1-10)
  - Selection of Lesbian/Gay Poetry (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - NAMBLA (North American Man/Boy Love Association) (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - National Center for Men (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Giovanni's Room (Gay/Lesbian bookstore, Philadelphia, PA) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Elizabeth Holtzman on "Invisible Diversity: A Gay and Lesbian Corporate Agenda" (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Gay Broadcasting System (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - COOL (Committee of Outraged Lesbians) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Alice Walker (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - WHAM (Women's Health Action and Mobilization) (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - WHAM (Women's Health Action and Mobilization) (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Reproductive Rights (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Activism: Women (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Gay/Lesbians of Color (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Black Lesbians and Gays (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - People of Color Conference - Chicago, April 1990 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - People of Color Conference (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - MACT (Men of All Colors Together): notes (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Responses to Supreme Court Webster Decision (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Que Viva! (Latino/a corporation in fine arts with Gay/Lesbian emphasis) (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - American Indian Community House Inc. (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - WE WAH and Indigenous People (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - National Coalition of Hispanic Health and Human Services Organizations (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - David Dinkins: Social Services Search Committee (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Universal Declaration of Human Rights (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Civil Rights (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Phil Zwickler Memorial (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Raymond Navarro (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Roy Navarro Memorial (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Loft Parties (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Humor (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Gay City Maps (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Maps (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Public Relations (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Exercise tips (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Tips on Public Speaking (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Kobena Mercer's article "Black Man's Sex" (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - New Canaan Weekend (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Religious/Spiritual Events (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Religious/Spiritual Events (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Thoreau's Civil Disobedience (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Miscellaneous activism including homelessness, nuclear disarmament, political asylum, human rights, peace, racism (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Miscellaneous Articles (Box 7, Folder 46-50)
  - Miscellaneous Clippings/Fliers (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Printed Material (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Single Issue Periodicals re Lesbians and Gays (Box 11, Folder 1-3)
  - Lesbian and Gay Community Services Center Garden Party Programs, 1989-1992 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - National Gay and Lesbian Task Force Conference Program, Nov. 10-12, 1990, Minnesota (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Single Issue Periodicals re HIV and AIDS (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Single Issue Periodicals re AIDS and Health Publications, special issues (Box 11, Folder 7-8)
  - Miscellaneous Single Issue Periodicals (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Single Issue Periodicals (Box 12, Folder 1-3)
- Series VI. Ephemera
  - Miscellaneous ephemera (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
  - Small pamphlet, various voices expressing anger about homophobia, titled "3," 198? (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Various quotations on slips of paper, notes, an invitation to a party (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Postcards, napkins (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Phonodiscs - 45 rpm (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - "March Madness" poster (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Assorted business cards (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Assorted buttons (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Assorted matchbooks (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Assorted name tags (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Assorted safe sex packets (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Assorted stickers (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Series VII. Graphic Material
  - Australian comicbook family violence, 1988, 1 (Box 9)
  - Flyers, materials on Science Fiction, 1989, 2 (Box 9)
  - Broadside: "Buddies in Bad Times Theatre Presents Queer Culture, Apr. 1991, 3 (Box 9)
  - Poster of the painting "Flandrin", 1982, 4 (Box 9)